Hello, everyone.
大家好。
So today we have quite a bit to cover.
今天我们有很多内容要讲解。
In particular, we are going to finish layering another king.
具体来说，我们将完成另一个层次的分层。
What we started last time.
我们上次开始的内容。
Then we are going to talk about end to end argument,
接下来我们将讨论端到端原则。
and we are going to then start the discussion on flow control.
然后我们将开始讨论流量控制。
So larry, so if you remember,
嗨，Larry，如果你还记得的话，
she just recap from the last time,
她只是简单回顾了上次的内容，
there are a few layers in the network has another king stack,
网络中有几个层次具有另一种协议栈。
has a few layers.
有几个层次。
In the internet, you have five layers.
在互联网中，你有五个层次。
The first layer at the bottom is physical layer.
底层的第一层是物理层。
And the role of the physical layer is to send the signal between two machines,
物理层的作用是在两台机器之间传输信号。
which are connected to the same transmission medium.
它们连接到相同的传输介质。
And the service is to move the information from one machine to another.
这项服务是将信息从一台机器转移到另一台机器。
The interface is about how to send and receive bids.
该接口是关于如何发送和接收竞标。
The protocol is about how these beats are encoding.
这个协议是关于如何对这些节拍进行编码的。
It's like based on the voltage duration of each bit frequency.
这类似于基于每个位频率的电压持续时间。
It's again, depending whether we are using the across your cable,
这取决于我们是否使用您的电缆。
optical fiber,
光纤
the wifi,
无线网络
and so forth.
等等，诸如此类。
The second layer is data link layer.
第二层是数据链路层。
Also, we discussed a little bit about it last time.
另外，上次我们也稍微讨论了一下。
The data link layer enables the host,
数据链路层使主机能够
which are on the same physical connected,
它们位于同一物理连接上，
the same physical network to exchange messages or atomic messages.
使用相同的物理网络来交换消息或原子消息。
Basically, the physical layer sends beats zero.
基本上，物理层发送的是零跳动。
And once here,
一旦到达这里，
we send packets.
我们发送数据包。
We send messages.
我们发送消息。
Also, they are called frames.
另外，它们被称为帧。
And what are the services here?
这里有哪些服务？
It's one it's about because you can have here multiple machines,
这是因为你可以在这里拥有多台机器。
which are connected,
这些是相互连接的。
may be on the cell physical line,
可能是在细胞物理线上。
or in the same wireless or the same wireless link.
或者在同一个无线网络或者同一个无线链路中。
There are multiple machines which can send data at the same time.
有多台机器可以同时发送数据。
So somehow you need to arbitrate to make sure that multiple senders
所以你需要进行仲裁，以确保多个发送者
do not call you.
请不要打电话给你。
This is very much like in a room in which everyone talk and talk with everyone.
这很像一个房间里每个人都在互相交谈的场景。
There has to be some kind of protocol so that not everyone stuck
必须有某种协议，以便不是每个人都被困住。
at the same time.
同时。
So people can understand each others.
这样人们就能互相理解了。
The interface is about how to send the frames to as over from one machine
接口是关于如何将帧从一台机器发送到另一台机器的方式。
to one horse to another horse.
给另一匹马。
And they also includes each frame includes an address,
并且每个帧还包括一个地址，
because this is how i'm going to indicate that I am going to send
因为这是我要发送信息的方式
a particular frame to a particular host is a list by destination address.
将特定帧发送给特定主机是根据目标地址进行列表化。
These addresses are the mac address,
这些地址是MAC地址。
is a media access or so called addresses or data link addresses.
媒体访问地址，也称为地址或数据链路地址。
And these are the ones, if you remember,
这些是那些，如果你还记得的话，
from last time,
从上次开始，
there are 48 beats,
一共有48个节拍。
and they are chosen by is a network card vendor.
它们是由网络卡供应商选择的。
So on that card,
那么在那张卡片上，
it's you create another card or you
是你创建另一张卡片还是我创建？
also associate address to it.
同时将地址与其关联。
And the protocol it's about like we discussed about how you
而且这个协议是关于我们之前讨论的内容，就是关于你如何
are going to arbitrate the access like to this shared communication
将要对这个共享通信的访问进行仲裁
media.
媒体。
Okay?
好的？
Each frame contains a source and a destination address.
每个帧都包含一个源地址和一个目的地址。
Each of them, again, is 48 bits.
每个都是48位。
And obviously,
显然，
this beats,
这是一种击败的方式。
this addresses are unique.
这些地址是唯一的。
Every network has a unique address.
每个网络都有一个唯一的地址。
You can also see these addresses,
您也可以查看这些地址，
like we discussed last time.
就像我们上次讨论的那样。
If you do ip configuring windows or if configuring linux,
如果你在配置Windows的IP或者配置Linux的IP，
here you can see these physical addresses is called,
这里你可以看到这些物理地址被称为
and this has 48 bits.
这个有48位。
You see.
你看到了。
123456.
And each of these groups has it in hexa.
每个组都以十六进制表示。
You have two digits,
你有两个数字，
and you have four beats for each digit.
每个数字有四个拍子。
You have,
你有，
in total, you have 48 weeks.
总共有48周。
Remember that the machine can have multiple network cards.
请记住，计算机可以有多个网络适配器。
So in this case, that's how you are going to see.
在这种情况下，这就是你将要看到的。
In two physical addresses.
使用两个物理地址。
In this case, one for the internet,
在这种情况下，一个用于互联网，
for the wire network, and one for the wireless network.
一个用于有线网络，一个用于无线网络。
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
So when I said that these hosts are connected with the same communication media,
当我说这些主机通过相同的通信介质连接时，
typically as a data link layer, this kind of metal,
通常作为数据链路层，这种金属材料，
the sharon at or two is a hostile connect again or communicate
Sharon在这里是一个敌对的连接，再次沟通或交流。
with each other is called land local area.
彼此之间连接的局域网被称为本地区域网。
Network.
网络。
And it's again examples are in a wireless network.
而且，它的例子再次是关于无线网络的。
It's all laptops in a starbucks affair,
这是关于在星巴克的一起笔记本电脑事件。
all for instance,
例如，
devices in your home or in your office.
您家里或办公室里的设备。
But this is a the key is that on all the devices connected with the same line,
但关键是所有连接在同一线路上的设备都是这样的。
can communicate with each other.
可以相互通信。
So you can think about this as a broadcast channel, a shared channel.
你可以将其视为广播通道，一个共享的通道。
This also means that when you send a packet or a frame,
这也意味着当你发送一个数据包或帧时，
that frame is going to be delivered to everyone.
那个帧将会被发送给每个人。
It's again like in the room,
又像在房间里一样，
when you say something loud enough,
当你大声说出某件事时，
everyone can hear.
每个人都可以听到。
Okay?
好的？
But now the obvious question is that if I want to send a frame
但现在显而易见的问题是，如果我想发送一个帧，应该怎么做呢？
to one particular post,
对于一个特定的帖子，
then how do I do it?
那么我该怎么做呢？
And obviously,
显然，
the answer here is that by indicating the destination address
这里的答案是通过指示目标地址来实现的。
of the recipient in the frame,
在帧中的接收者
in this example,
在这个例子中，
if I am going to send,
如果我要发送，
I want to send to ba wants to send a frame to b is going to put the address
我想发送给B的帧，将要放置地址。
or to be in the frame as a destination address.
或者作为目标地址的一部分。
Now, because this is a broadcast,
现在，因为这是一个广播，
the line is a broadcast channel.
这条线是一个广播通道。
This packet will be delivered to every host in the network.
这个数据包将会发送给网络中的每个主机。
However,
然而，
each host can check whether the data frames are intended to itself by checking
每个主机可以通过检查数据帧是否是针对自己的来确定。
its own mac address against the destination address in the frame.
它会将自己的MAC地址与帧中的目标地址进行比对。
If they are the same,
如果它们是相同的，
then it accepts a packet,
然后它接收一个数据包，
otherwise it drops back.
否则它会回退。
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
It's like in our examples.
就像我们的例子一样。
If you are going to speak loudly and everyone can hear,
如果你要大声说话，让每个人都能听到，
if you want to,
如果你愿意的话，
say, address to your friend,
嘿，朋友，
john, you basically say, hey, john,
约翰，你基本上说，嘿，约翰，
and then you are going to say whatever you have to say.
然后你可以说出你想说的任何话。
Right?
对吗？
And by that,
而且，
this means that journal pay attention,
这意味着期刊要注意，
and maybe the other people do not pay attention because that message is
而且可能其他人没有注意到，因为那条信息是
not intelligent.
不智能的。
Now, the land can be larger,
现在，土地可以更大了，
can include multiple hundreds of machines.
可以包括数百台机器。
When includes hundreds of machines or a large number of larger number of machines,
当涉及到数百台机器或大量更多的机器时，
typically they are connected by switches.
通常它们通过交换机连接。
Switches are a little more intelligent.
交换机更加智能。
And so basically,
所以基本上，
switches are doing some pruning of the messages.
交换机正在对消息进行一些修剪。
So if I switch,
那么如果我转换的话，
get some message is it's and that is the horse is not behind.
获取一些信息，它是这样的，那匹马不在后面。
One of its connections is not going to send that frame on that connection.
其中一个连接不会在该连接上发送该帧。
In this particular case, for instance,
在这个特定的情况下，例如，
when b arrives at the switch,
当 b 到达交换机时，
the switch will directly send to be is not going to deliver to bnc it's a feature.
交换机将直接发送给B，而不会传递给BNC，这是一项功能。
It's more efficient.
这样更高效。
But I can that's why the switches are.
但是我可以，这就是开关的作用。
In general when you have a lot of machines,
一般来说，当你有很多台机器时，
what is very inefficient for that frame to be sent to add to reach everyone?
将该帧发送到每个地址以达到所有人的目的非常低效。
Questions?
有问题吗？
How can we ensure mac addresses are unique?
我们如何确保MAC地址的唯一性？
This is excellent question.
这是一个很棒的问题。
Typically, every network vendor,
通常情况下，每个网络供应商，
it's assigned a block of mac addresses.
它被分配了一组 MAC 地址。
And he that vendor can only associate the mac
只有该供应商才能关联该MAC地址。
addresses in his blog to all the network,
他在博客中公开了所有网络的地址。
to all the network cards it produces.
对所有它所生产的网络卡。
That's ha.
哈哈。
No news.
没有新闻。
So another great question is this where security concerns come in?
另一个很好的问题是安全问题出现在哪里？
Can a horse who has a packet is not addressed to still read the message?
一个没有被寻址的马是否能读取到这个消息？
Yes.
是的。
It's an opec.
这是一个OPEC。
That's why you are told that when you are going to be in,
这就是为什么你被告知当你要进入时，
a starter started by scofield,
由斯科菲尔德启动的一个启动器
what you are going to be, you are told, right?
你被告知你将要成为什么，对吗？
You need to use encryption.
你需要使用加密。
Why do you want to use encryption?
为什么你想要使用加密？
Because you don't want just someone to snoop on your own snoopy
因为你不希望有人窥探你的窥探行为
on your packets and read everything what you send or receive.
在你的数据包上进行监视并阅读你发送或接收的所有内容。
Great questions.
很好的问题。
Michael, here is another great question.
迈克尔，这是又一个很棒的问题。
How does the switch now that mac address of b does a device declare
设备如何声明自己的 MAC 地址，交换机是如何知道设备 b 的 MAC 地址的？
its address open connecting to a new media?
它的地址是打开连接到新媒体吗？
There is a special protocol by which the devices connect,
设备之间有一种特殊的协议用于连接。
and then they advertise their address, the switch.
然后他们宣传他们的地址，交换机。
Excellent questions.
非常好的问题。
Please keep them coming.
请继续发送。
Now, one of our problem is, again,
现在，我们的一个问题是，再次，
now let's think about, again,
现在让我们再次思考一下，
these broadcast media,
这些广播媒体，
because even with a switch,
因为即使有一个交换机，
with a switch here,
这里使用一个开关。
we are simplifying it,
我们正在简化它。
but behind each of this output of the switch,
但在每个交换机的输出背后，
there are many hosts.
有许多主机。
It's not only one host still there.
不仅仅还有一个主机存在。
You still have in by this,
你仍然在这里。
that almost by definition,
几乎可以说是根据定义，
in a land,
在一个国家中，
you have multiple hosts being able to send and receive packets at the same time.
你有多个主机可以同时发送和接收数据包。
And when you have multiple people, say,
当你有多个人时，比如说，
sorry, multiple hosts sending being able to send back at the same time,
抱歉，多个主机同时发送并能够同时回复。
you need to somehow make sure they don't collide.
你需要确保它们不会发生碰撞。
Right?
对吗？
And there are three solutions,
有三种解决方案，
a channel partition, taking turns,
通道分区，轮流进行
and random access.
和随机访问。
Channel partition is basically think about you have different frequencies.
通道分区基本上是指你拥有不同的频率。
This is 11 typical example.
这是一个典型的例子。
What you do is frequency division multiplex.
你所做的是频分复用。
You have a band of frequency,
你有一个频率带。
and you are going to split that band in different kinds of frequencies.
你将把这个频带分成不同的频率。
And then you allocate one of these frequency to a different host.
然后你将其中一个频率分配给另一个主机。
And each host can only send on that frequency.
每个主机只能在那个频率上发送。
And you can listen for multiple frequencies,
而且你可以同时监听多个频率，
so you can get the packers from on any frequency.
所以你可以在任何频率上获取到打包者。
Right?
对吗？
Now, what are the advantage of that?
那么，这有什么优势呢？
Is simple.
很简单。
It's pretty clear.
非常清楚。
It provides also some isolation.
它还提供了一些隔离性。
You have your own frequency.
你有自己的频率。
You don't care about the other people you can send on your own frequency.
你不在乎其他人，你可以自己发送信息。
You don't care about other costs.
你不关心其他费用。
It's a pretty efficient.
这非常高效。
One is very high load.
一个问题是负载非常高。
When the load is small,
当负载较小时，
then it's very inefficient.
那么它就非常低效。
Because from if all, for instance,
因为从如果所有的情况来看，例如，
you have only one host sending to another host, right?
你只有一个主机发送给另一个主机，对吗？
Out of 100 hostels there.
共有100个旅馆。
Then you can use only one,
那么你只需要使用一个。
1% of the entire frequency range,
整个频率范围的1%
the ones that frequency,
频率较高的那些
which is allocated with that particular host itself,
这是分配给特定主机的。
while the other one are not yours.
而另一个不是你的。
Ideally,
理想情况下，
what you would like is that of the only two machine to host or communicate
您希望的是只有两台机器进行主机或通信。
with each other,
彼此之间，
you should and none of the others send data.
只有你应该发送数据，其他人都不需要发送。
You should these two holes should be able to use the entire frequency range.
这两个孔应该能够使用整个频率范围。
The other one is pretty similar,
另一个则非常相似，
but this is resource,
但这是资源，
but instead of dividing the frequencies,
但是不是将频率进行分割，
it divides a time.
它将时间分割。
So basically, here,
基本上，在这里，
it's you have imagine that you have a talk.
你可以想象一下你正在进行一次对话。
A talking is a special budget.
"Talking" refers to a conversation or discussion. "A special budget" means a specific or unique financial plan.
And the stock on is going.
股票正在上涨。
And again,
再次，
you can think about that hosts are organized in a logical drink.
你可以将主机组织成一个逻辑饮料。
For instance, okay,
例如，好的，
then this stock and goes from horse to horse around the ring.
然后这只股票在赛马场上从一匹马转到另一匹马。
Now, you can send data only while when you have the top,
现在，只有在你拥有顶部时才能发送数据。
if you have data to send,
如果你有要发送的数据，
but you don't have the token.
但是你没有令牌。
You need to wait to receive the token.
你需要等待接收令牌。
So again, because it's only one post has a token at a given time.
所以，再次强调，因为在给定时间只有一个帖子有一个令牌。
You are sure you are ensuring that there is no collision,
你确保没有发生碰撞。
because only one horse can send up a given time.
因为一次只能发送一匹马。
Again, you have the same kind of a little bit issues.
再次，你有一些小问题。
When everyone has things to send is working great,
当每个人都有东西要发送时，一切都运行得很顺利。
because you get a token,
因为你获得了一个令牌，
you already have,
你已经拥有了。
you send data, you have to send data.
当你发送数据时，你必须发送数据。
If only two hosts,
如果只有两个主机，
one host has to send data to another host,
一个主机需要将数据发送给另一个主机。
then it's more problematic,
那么问题就更加棘手了，
because you need to wait for every other host around the ring to get.
因为你需要等待环形中的每个其他主机都收到。
There is and send out the token before you can send the next packet.
在发送下一个数据包之前，必须先发送并传递令牌。
It's kind of an overhead,
这有点额外负担。
just waiting for this token,
只是在等待这个令牌，
to go around,
绕过，绕行
just for each host to pass it,
每个主机都要通过它。
who doesn't have anything to send just to pass it to another,
没有任何东西需要发送，只是将其传递给另一个人的人。
the next force.
下一个力量。
They just pure overhead,
它们只是纯粹的开销。
which reduces the efficiency of this protocol.
这会降低该协议的效率。
And finally,
最后，
it's random axis.
这是随机轴。
It's also its carrier sense.
这也是它的载波侦听。
Collision detection is called csma this is infinite.
碰撞检测被称为CSMA，这是无限的。
If you heard, this is probably the most popular data link layer technology.
如果你听说过的话，这可能是最流行的数据链路层技术。
Right?
对吗？
And a form of this is also you have for wireless.
而且你们也有无线的一种形式。
But here this is exactly to better understand it.
但是在这里，这正是为了更好地理解它。
Imagine, again,
再次想象一下，
there is a room full of people and they are talking right.
有一个房间里挤满了人，他们正在交谈。
Now, imagine that again,
现在，请再次想象一下，
everyone hears everyone.
每个人都听到了每个人的声音。
So the room is small enough.
房间足够小。
So what do you do?
那你做什么工作？
Right?
对吗？
First of all,
首先，
before you speak,
在你说话之前，
you listen a little bit, right?
你有听到一点点，对吗？
This is scarier sense.
这是一种更可怕的感觉。
You listen that it's a pause.
你听到了一段停顿。
No one else is talking.
没有其他人在说话。
Right?
对吗？
You also don't interrupt, right?
你也不会打断，对吧？
Someone.
有人。
So if someone is though is talking,
那么如果有人正在说话，
you wait for that person to finish before you start that.
在开始之前，请等待那个人完成。
This is for life.
这是为了生活。
This is scary of sense, right?
这感觉很可怕，对吧？
Someone is the medium.
有人是中介。
It's busy because there are some packets being sent out.
忙是因为有一些数据包正在发送出去。
Then you wait for a pause for the media to be idol.
然后你等待媒体停止播放的间隙。
Before it.
在此之前。
You said this is not enough to avoid the collisions,
你说这还不足以避免碰撞。
because more many people may have like in our analogy,
因为更多的人可能会喜欢我们的类比。
As a room analogy.
作为一个房间的比喻。
Multiple people may wait for the current speaker to finish to say something,
多个人可能会等待当前发言者结束后再说些什么。
sometimes happens that people can start to people to start talking
有时候人们会开始聊天。
at the same time.
同时。
Now, that's a collision the same here.
现在，这里也发生了碰撞。
When the media is either to horse,
当媒体要么太过激动，
are going to send back at the same time,
会同时发送回去吗？
these factors are going to collide.
这些因素将会发生碰撞。
Right?
对吗？
What do you do that?
为什么要这样做？
It's again, assuming that you are polite,
再次假设你是礼貌的，
you are most people who like start talking at the same time.
你是那种喜欢同时开始说话的人。
This when they stop,
这是他们停下来的时候，
right?
对的？
They stopped for a while and then try again.
他们停下来一会儿，然后再试一次。
Right?
对吗？
Sometimes again,
有时候再次，
it's like,
就像是，
as you probably,
正如你可能已经注意到的，
i'm sure you witness that two people start at the same time stop and then again,
我确定你目睹了两个人同时开始、停下，然后再次开始的情况。
start at the same time.
同时开始。
So we want to avoid that here in the design of this protocol.
因此，在这个协议的设计中，我们希望避免这种情况发生。
And how do you design it?
你是指操作系统的设计吗？
Each of the parties, each of the hosts,
每个派对，每个主办方，
if there is a collision,
如果发生碰撞，
waits for a random amount of time.
等待一个随机的时间。
If you wait for a random amount of time,
如果你等待一个随机的时间，
the probability of collision, again, colliding again,
再次发生碰撞的概率
is lower.
是较低的。
This is pretty much it.
就是这样了。
Right?
对吗？
And it's very simple.
而且它非常简单。
It decentralized.
它是去中心化的。
It works pretty well.
它运行得相当不错。
In practice,
在实践中，
it's beautiful protocol.
这是一个很美的协议。
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
It's again the token you can assume this is again like this protocol,
这个令牌是指你可以假设这个协议再次如此。
the cmic csmacd it's like think about always like the protocol,
CMIC CSMACD就像是一直在思考协议一样。
people who use polite people who used in a room or speaking with each other.
在一个房间里或者彼此交谈时使用礼貌的人。
This token protocol,
这个令牌协议，
I will discuss in the previous slide,
我将在前一张幻灯片中讨论。
the taking turns.
轮流。
You can imagine it's like only people who have the mic are going to talk.
你可以想象成只有拿着麦克风的人才能说话。
Right?
对吗？
When you ask questions like a conference and so forth.
当你像在会议上提问等等的时候。
When you ask questions, there is a mic.
当你提问时，有一个麦克风。
If there is only one mic,
如果只有一个麦克风，
only someone is going to hand the mic is a person who has who can tell who
只有拿着麦克风的人才能告诉我们是谁
wants to ask a question,
想要提问一个问题，
but only the person who has a mic.
但只有有麦克风的人可以。
And as a question.
作为一个问题。
So there are no apologies.
所以没有道歉。
So let's see.
那么让我们来看看。
Why would I want allison has this question?
为什么我想要Allison有这个问题？
Why would I want my computer to play fair?
为什么我希望我的计算机公平地运行？
Can I configure my computer to just shoot over everyone?
我可以配置我的计算机只射击所有人吗？
So then it will be faster.
那么它将会更快。
I think that's a good point.
我认为这是一个很好的观点。
The problem, though,
然而，问题是，
is that if everyone is doing the same or even,
这意味着如果每个人都在做同样的事情，甚至是相等的事情。
other people don't do exactly the same,
其他人不会完全做一样的事情，
you are going to have collisions.
你会发生碰撞。
And if you have collisions, you have garbage, you cannot be hurt.
如果发生碰撞，就会产生垃圾，你不会受到伤害。
That's a problem.
这是一个问题。
Right?
对吗？
You cannot, in some sense,
在某种意义上，你无法
you cannot increase the intensity of your signal.
你无法增加信号的强度。
So probably in this case,
所以在这种情况下，
you don't have the ability to increase that kind of intensity.
你没有能力增加那种强度。
Like in practice,
就像在实践中一样，
maybe you are going to yell.
也许你要大声喊叫。
Your voice will be stronger than anyone else,
你的声音将比任何人都更强大，
but here everyone is on the level playing field.
但在这里，每个人都处于公平竞争的环境中。
The same you can send only beats the same visa services against the same voltage,
相同的电压下，只有相同的节拍才能击败相同的签证服务。
the same density,
相同的密度
if two people, if 2 horses,
如果有两个人，如果有2匹马，
and at the same time,
同时，
these are going to be interference.
这些将会产生干扰。
And your message is not going to be delivered to the destination.
您的消息将无法传递到目的地。
Simon,
Simon，
你好，有什么我可以帮助你的吗？
how does random access guarantee a node ever get a chance to speak?
随机访问如何保证每个节点都有机会发言？
What if in the random someone is always speaking when I try to speak?
如果在随机的情况下，每当我试图说话时，总有人在说话，该怎么办？
Could that cause a starvation?
这可能会导致饥饿现象吗？
That's a great question.
这是一个很好的问题。
And it's probabilistic.
而且它是概率性的。
It's like,
就像是，
you,
你
there is a the probability that you are going to be able to speak is non zero.
你有一定的概率能够说话，概率不为零。
Now, it turns out that this random access protocols,
现在，事实证明这种随机访问协议，
they work very well.
它们工作得非常好。
You remember this as a token that the token protocol and the one and with
你将这个记住作为一个令牌，令牌协议和一个与之相关的。
a frequency division multiplexing,
频分复用
they are working very well.
他们工作得非常好。
When the system is very utilized,
当系统被高度利用时，
this is highly utilized when everyone copies everyone.
当每个人都互相抄袭时，这就被广泛利用了。
But it doesn't have such a high efficiency when the system is now utilized,
但是当系统目前被利用时，它的效率并不是很高。
because that say,
因为那样说，
if you have only to host talking to each other,
如果你只有两个主机彼此交流，
they cannot use the entire frequency range,
他们无法使用整个频率范围。
or they have to wait for the token to get around only for and all the other
或者他们必须等待令牌传递到他们这里，然后才能进行操作，而其他人也是一样的。
was not doing anything with the doctor.
没有和医生做任何事情。
This is a reverse,
这是一个反向操作。
is working extremely well on another piece is lightly utilized,
在另一台轻负载的设备上运行得非常好。
because there are no collisions.
因为没有发生碰撞。
But when these heavily utilized,
但是当这些被广泛使用时，
there are many collisions,
发生了许多碰撞。
then the efficiency is going down.
那么效率就会下降。
So there is a problem with that.
所以有一个问题。
And but again,
而但是再次，
so this is probably the intuition behind your question,
所以这可能是你提问的直觉背后的原因，
simon.
西蒙。
But in theory,
但是从理论上讲，
you are going to get your thought.
你将要得到你的想法。
It's like,
就像是，
think about the one.
思考那个人。
It's like here is another analogy.
这里有另一个类比。
You are coming from a secondary road.
你是从一条次要道路上来的。
You are in the main road and you don't have a priority and you want to take
你现在在主干道上，没有优先权，但你想要通过。
the right or less.
右边或更少。
Right?
对吗？
Like you go from,
就像你从...开始，
say, for you whatever you exit, right?
你是说，无论你退出什么，都可以吗？
So you need to wait for a gap to get to enter the traffic.
所以你需要等待一个空隙才能进入交通流。
And in theory,
理论上来说，
you may never get that bad that gap.
你可能永远不会遇到那么糟糕的差距。
But in practice,
但在实践中，
you don't know you did not need to wait too much.
你不知道你不需要等太久。
So probabilistic really is not salvation.
所以概率性真的不是救世主。
The next is a network layer.
接下来是网络层。
I don't know, I so need to update this figure.
我不知道，我非常需要更新这个数字。
On the right hand side.
在右侧。
We are talking about the network layer.
我们正在讨论网络层。
The network layer is actually the most important.
网络层实际上是最重要的。
In some sense.
在某种意义上。
When you talk about internet,
当谈到互联网时，
internet is the main layer in the internet is the internet protocol.
互联网是互联网协议中的主要层级。
Or ip you heard about the ip right?
你是否听说过知识产权（IP）呢？
Ip is the internet proposal is another class.
IP是互联网协议的另一个类别。
The network player had its own address.
网络播放器有自己的地址。
They are called ip addresses.
它们被称为IP地址。
And every host a as a unique ip address.
每个主机都有一个唯一的IP地址。
And this is global,
而且这是全球性的，
it says the level of the entire planet.
它表示整个地球的水平。
So nathara blair is basically going to be able to ensure the main service
所以Nathara Blair基本上将能够确保主要服务的运行
is going to ensure its connectivity.
将确保其连接性。
You can deliver a packet,
你可以传递一个数据包。
specifying the network address or the ip address across the globe.
指定全球范围内的网络地址或IP地址。
From new york, tokyo,
从纽约到东京
from a network in europe,
来自欧洲的一个网络
from a host in san francisco to a host in tokyo.
从旧金山的主机到东京的主机。
This will be across multiple data link layer methods,
这将涉及多个数据链路层方法，
because you cannot have just a data link layer network over the entire globe.
因为你不能仅仅通过数据链路层在全球范围内建立网络。
There are possible other services,
可能还有其他服务。
like scheduling priorities,
像调度优先级，
or some packets are more important than the other.
或者有些数据包比其他的更重要。
You can think about.
你可以考虑一下。
Video packets are going to have higher priorities,
视频数据包将具有更高的优先级。
and data packets seem like that.
数据包看起来就像这样。
You need also to handle the buffer management.
你还需要处理缓冲区管理。
The packets, along the way,
在传输过程中的数据包
are going to be buffer.
将要成为缓冲区。
The interface is very simple.
界面非常简单。
You send a packet to a specify not address this image,
你发送了一个数据包到一个指定的非地址的图像。
and you receive that packet,
然后你收到了那个数据包，
which is intended to you.
这是针对你的。
The protocol includes defining these network addresses which are
协议包括定义这些网络地址，它们是：
globally unique and also constructed the router what are called
全球唯一的，并且构建了所谓的路由器。
forwarding tables.
转发表。
So a router which connects a router,
所以一个连接两个路由器的路由器，
connects different and locality and adults.
连接不同的地方和成年人。
It receives a packet.
它接收到一个数据包。
It looks at the destination address and decides where to send it out.
它查看目标地址并决定将其发送到哪里。
This is the metal player.
这是金属播放器。
And you see the metal player packet.
你可以看到金属玩家的数据包。
It has a payload and the head they are encapsulated in a data frame.
它有一个负载和头部，它们被封装在数据帧中。
Encapsulation means that you take a packet from the metal player and you
封装意味着你从物理层接收一个数据包，并将其封装成更高层的协议中。
add the head of the frame.
添加帧的头部。
This becomes a frame.
这变成了一个帧。
The other header contains the ip destination address and the ip source others.
另一个头部包含了IP目标地址和IP源地址。
And as I mentioned to you,
正如我之前跟你提到的，
these are routed by the routers,
这些被路由器路由。
connect different data link that data layer methods.
连接不同的数据链路层方法。
And all this aggregation of local area matters is called a wide area network.
所有这些局域网的聚合被称为广域网。
So now what is the difference between the switch and the router?
现在，交换机和路由器有什么区别呢？
It's simple.
很简单。
The router, it's only it recognizes and routes based on the ip addresses.
路由器只能根据IP地址识别和路由数据。
A switch,
一个交换机
it's only in a local area network and only recognize mac addresses,
它只在局域网中工作，并且只识别MAC地址。
sort out the function like I mentioned,
整理出我提到的那个函数。
his father, it's to get the packets,
他的父亲，是为了获取数据包。
look at their heads and decide on which output link to send them.
观察他们的头部并决定将他们发送到哪个输出链路。
This is how the router works.
这是路由器的工作原理。
You have a bunch of incoming links,
你有一堆传入链接。
you get pakistan,
你得到了巴基斯坦。
and out outgoing links.
入站链接和出站链接。
It's like a huge intersection.
它就像一个巨大的交叉口。
Right?
对吗？
And basically, what router implements a mechanics,
基本上，路由器实现了一种机制，
which is called store and forward store and forward means the packets
这被称为存储转发，存储转发意味着数据包。
are received first are stored.
首先接收到的被存储。
And after a store,
在存储之后，
the router inspects the header.
路由器检查头部信息。
And based on the destination of the others decides where the forwards
根据其他人的目的地决定转发的位置
and they are stored because you
它们被存储起来是因为你需要将它们保留下来。
don't want to drop the package if the router cannot process them fast enough.
如果路由器无法快速处理数据包，不想丢弃这些数据包。
Does it be?
是吗？
Again,
请再说一遍。
the forwarding table is a mapping between ip addresses and the output.
转发表是IP地址和输出之间的映射关系。
Right here is an example about the packet going from host a to host each
这里是一个关于数据包从主机A到主机B的示例。
other or decide to watch output goes to forward the packet based on its ip address.
其他路由器或决定观察输出的设备会根据其IP地址转发数据包。
And based on the information is a forwarding paper.
根据提供的信息，这是一份转发文件。
So now this life is very important,
所以现在这个生活非常重要，
because it's obvious question.
因为这是一个显而易见的问题。
Now.
现在。
I have mac addresses,
我有MAC地址。
and you told me that they are unique.
你告诉我它们是独一无二的。
Now you tell me also about ip addresses which are also unique.
现在你也告诉我关于IP地址的事情，它们也是唯一的。
Why do I need to kind of others?
为什么我需要善待他人？
Why not using a single type of others?
为什么不使用单一类型的其他人？
In particular, why shouldn't I use as a mac address for output?
特别是，为什么我不能将其用作输出的 MAC 地址？
I already have this.
我已经有这个了。
Why do I need another address?
为什么我需要另一个地址？
The answer is that remember how the mac addresses are allocated?
答案是记住 MAC 地址是如何分配的吗？
I am a network card vendor.
我是一家网络卡供应商。
I get a block of macolysis.
我遇到了一个宏解析的问题。
And i'm going to use this address is in the block to assign to my net of cards.
我将使用这个地址块中的地址来分配给我的网络卡。
It's not.
不是的。
Okay.
好的。
And then these network cards are in computers which are all over the globe.
然后这些网络卡安装在遍布全球的计算机中。
So there is no aggregation is very much like social security number.
所以聚合就像社会安全号码一样没有什么不同。
Now I am asking you,
现在我在问你，
i'm giving you a social security number,
我正在提供给你一个社会安全号码，
right?
是的，没错。
Let's say they are not private.
假设它们不是私有的。
They are not confidential.
它们不是机密的。
And i'm telling you, hey,
我告诉你，嘿，
deliver this letter message to this social security number,
将这封信件的信息发送给这个社会安全号码。
123456, whatever.
123456，随便。
How easy is that?
那有多容易？
Or how hard is it?
或者说它有多难？
It's pretty hard because there is now they are random across the globe.
这很困难，因为现在它们在全球范围内都是随机的。
Now, to compare that,
现在，为了进行比较，
if I am going to give you a message or a letter to deliver,
如果我要给你一条信息或一封信让你传递，
i'm telling you what is the home address of the recipient.
我告诉你收件人的家庭地址是什么。
It's much easier because the others are structured.
这更容易，因为其他的都是有结构的。
Right?
对吗？
The only thing, for instance,
例如，唯一的事情是
say,
说,
i'm going to send the address to this17th street and northwest washington,
我将发送地址给你，这是在华盛顿西北部的第17街。
dc and so forth.
等等等等。
If i'm sending it from california,
如果我从加利福尼亚发送的话，
only the first thing I need to know is that is going to washington,
我只需要知道的第一件事是，它要去华盛顿吗？
dc so I put it on a plane to go to washington,
所以我把它装上飞机去华盛顿。
dc that's the only thing it's very easy.
dc，那是唯一的事情，非常容易。
Right?
对吗？
The amount of state I can use in san francisco to say i'm going to send
我可以在旧金山使用的州份数量，以表明我要发送的内容。
the packet.
数据包。
The letter is very small, right?
这封信非常小，对吗？
Only the cities or the states or the country.
只有城市、州或国家。
If I am sending international letter,
如果我要寄国际信件，
once the letter is coming, going to washington,
一旦信件到达，就会前往华盛顿。
dc remains in the washington dc area.
dc仍然位于华盛顿特区。
And then I know i'm going to look at the street,
然后我知道我要看街道了。
and then i'm looking at the others for this.
然后我会看看其他人对此的看法。
So you can have this theoretical structure and routing of the letter
所以你可以拥有这封信的理论结构和路由
from the sender to the recipient.
从发送者到接收者。
This is what the ip address gives you this structure who is much will make
这是IP地址提供的结构，它会提供很多信息。
it much easier.
这样会容易得多。
I and then if i'm sending from that on to someone from california,
如果我从那里发送给加利福尼亚的某人，
from berkeley, it's again,
来自伯克利，又是我。
just look at the berkeley first sent to berkeley to or someone
请先查看伯克利发送给伯克利或其他人的信息。
close to back san francisco,
靠近旧金山后方。
auckland,
奥克兰
a on a plane to auckland.
在飞往奥克兰的飞机上。
And from there is going to be delivered to you.
然后将从那里送到您那里。
Any question?
有任何问题吗？
So fundamentally, it's, again,
从根本上说，再次强调，
the ip addresses have structured geographic structure,
IP地址具有结构化的地理结构。
the political structure.
政治结构。
And therefore,
因此，
they can be aggregated aggravated.
它们可以被聚合或加重。
Therefore, the following tables in the routers can be much smaller.
因此，路由器中的以下表格可以更小。
Right?
对吗？
While for mac addresses,
对于MAC地址，
there is no aggregation,
没有聚合
we need to keep a following table,
我们需要维护一个以下的表格：
which is equally the number of mechanisms,
这同样是机制的数量，
existing market analysis,
现有市场分析
which is huge casing..
这是一个巨大的机箱。
Assume that you want to send a packet from
假设你想要从一台计算机发送一个数据包到另一台计算机。
new york to a particular ip address to a particular host in uzbek.
从纽约到乌兹别克斯坦的特定IP地址的特定主机。
Then they use it.
然后他们使用它。
Berkeley.
伯克利。
Actually, all ip addresses are starting with this.
实际上，所有的 IP 地址都以这个开头。
The first are 2 bytes,
第一个是2个字节。
are all common, a 95.
都是常见的，95分。
So the router in new york,
所以纽约的路由器，
it needs to keep only one entry for all hosts,
它需要仅保留一个条目用于所有主机，
which are in you associated with this directly.
你直接与此相关的是哪些？
If you don't have that and you use mike addresses,
如果你没有那个并且你使用了错误的地址，
then the new router has to keep an entry for every host,
那么新路由器必须为每个主机保留一个条目。
which is much harder and much harder to update,
这是更加困难且更加难以更新的。
maintain, and things like that.
维护，以及诸如此类的事情。
Does it make sense?
这有意义吗？
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
So to summarize here,
所以在这里总结一下，
ssn mac address like ssn and an ip address is like an address,
SSN（社会安全号码）类似于MAC地址，而IP地址则类似于物理地址。
although it's not readable.
尽管它不可读。
Right?
对吗？
So therefore, it's much easier to build a system like a male system.
因此，构建一个像男性系统那样的系统要容易得多。
In our case,
在我们的情况下，
to deliver the letter to a particular address, which has structured,
将信件送到一个特定的地址，该地址已经有结构化的形式。
then to some identifier,
然后给某个标识符赋值。
Which has no structure.
没有结构。
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
Like I mentioned, this is the internet protocol,
就像我之前提到的，这是互联网协议。
the international player,
国际球员
and the internet protocol is the internet senator player.
互联网协议是互联网的核心组成部分。
The service it provides.
它提供的服务。
It's got its connectivity and back at delivery.
它已经恢复了连接，并已经交付。
But its best effort means that you are not guaranteed that your packet
但是“尽力而为”意味着你不能保证你的数据包
is going to make the destination.
即将到达目的地。
It may be dropped, it may be corrupted.
它可能会被丢弃，也可能会被损坏。
And also,
而且，
it doesn't guarantee that the package will send two packets on out of one
这并不能保证该包将发送两个数据包中的一个。
after another.
之后的另一个。
They are going to arrive at the same time in the same order,
他们将以相同的顺序同时到达。
because they may follow different routes.
因为它们可能会选择不同的路径。
It's like,
就像是，
you cannot guarantee that two cars which started san francisco and arrive
你不能保证两辆从旧金山出发并到达的汽车
to and are driving to la they are going to get that delay the same work.
他们正在开车去洛杉矶，他们打算在那里遇到同样的工作延误。
It's very simple.
这很简单。
Now,
现在，
on top of the metal layer,
在金属层的顶部
you have transport layer and the transport layer provide.
你有传输层，传输层提供了什么功能。
It's one level up.
它上升了一个级别。
The net of layer deliver a packet from one horse to an ass.
网络层将一个数据包从一匹马传递到一头驴。
But the hosts do not consume the packet.
但是主机不会消耗数据包。
Application consumes the packet.
应用程序消耗了数据包。
And the application is a process.
应用程序是一个进程。
On a machine have multiple processes.
在一台机器上有多个进程。
You need to specify to which packet to each process on a particular machine.
你需要为特定机器上的每个进程指定要发送的数据包。
The packet needs to be delivered.
这个数据包需要被传送。
The ip address of the recipient is not enough.
收件人的IP地址不足够。
Read another thing to differentiate between multiple processes running
阅读另一篇文章以区分多个正在运行的进程。
on the same action on the same course.
在同一门课程上进行相同的操作。
This is a port.
这是一个端口。
Now.
现在。
I could see.
我明白了。
So the transfer layer,
因此，传输层是一个重要的网络层，它负责在源主机和目标主机之间提供可靠的数据传输。传输层使用传输协议来分割和重组数据，以确保数据的完整性和可靠性。常见的传输协议包括TCP（传输控制协议）和UDP（用户数据报协议）。
multiplex and the multiplex packets,
多路复用和多路复用数据包
which arrive on the same post,
同时到达的邮件
that as other services can provide the reliability,
其他服务也可以提供可靠性，
right?
对的？
Adaptation, like we discussed last time, flow control, congestion control,
适应性，就像我们上次讨论的那样，流量控制，拥塞控制。
and timing properties.
以及时间属性。
Maybe they are going to.
也许他们会这样做。
You've got a guarantee that the packet will be delivered within 100 millisecond.
你可以确保数据包在100毫秒内被传送。
It's important, say, for voice communication,
这很重要，比如说，对于语音通信来说，
the interface is the same message to a specific process of a given estimation.
接口是发送给特定进程的给定估计的相同消息。
And the local process receives a message sent to it.
本地进程接收到发送给它的消息。
The protocol includes the poor numbers.
该协议包括贫穷数。
We used to differentiate between different processes.
我们过去会区分不同的进程。
It may implement reliability,
它可能实现可靠性，
flow control,
流量控制
and packet is asian because of my sense bigger,
"packet" 是亚洲人的称呼，因为我感觉亚洲人的体型较大。
depending on the interface,
根据接口的不同，
you may send streams.
你可以发送数据流。
Like if you remember,
如果你还记得的话，
we have this kind of interface to the network.
我们有这种与网络连接的接口。
You have blocked and stream interface from the stream interface.
你已经从流接口中阻止了流接口。
Somehow you need to chop these streams into packets and send these packets.
你需要将这些流切割成数据包并发送这些数据包。
That is a higher level.
那是一个较高级别的。
You have the transfer layer,
你有传输层。
you have a transfer header.
你有一个传输头。
The transport header is a protocol number as the for port numbers.
传输头部是一个协议号，类似于端口号。
And you have also like, for instance, 80,
而且你还有，例如，80个。
it's identifies for the port is reallocated the port for hpv server.
它标识端口已重新分配给hpv服务器。
There are two important transport protocols in the internet using udp
在互联网中，有两个重要的传输协议使用UDP。
user data ground protocol.
用户数据地面协议。
And this provides only multiplexing and multiplexing among processes.
这只提供了进程之间的多路复用和多路复用。
This is the best effort.
这是最好的努力。
Backers can be lost, can get out of order.
支持者可能会丢失，也可能会顺序错乱。
There is no flow control, nothing.
没有流量控制，什么都没有。
The application is to take care of.
这个应用程序需要照顾。
Then it's pcp which is a transport control protocol.
那么它就是一个传输控制协议（PCP）。
This obviously still provides multiplexing and in multiplexing around processes.
这显然仍然提供了多路复用和在进程之间的多路复用。
But in addition, has a notion of connection.
此外，还具有连接的概念。
You set up the connection and tear down the connection.
你建立连接并拆除连接。
If there are packets which are corrupted or corrupted, you discard them.
如果有损坏或错误的数据包，你应该将其丢弃。
There is a check sum.
有一个校验和。
You check.
你检查。
If the check sum is violated,
如果校验和被破坏，
you discuss the packet.
你讨论数据包。
It transmits a lost packet.
它传输了一个丢失的数据包。
A self provides reliability to the application,
自我为应用程序提供可靠性。
and it's also provides flow control and condition control.
它还提供了流程控制和条件控制。
Remember, flow control is about not overwhelming.
记住，流量控制是为了避免过载。
The receiver.
接收器。
The congestion control is not overwhelming.
拥塞控制并不压倒性。
The method,
该方法，
the services are not typically available.
这些服务通常不可用。
Any bandwidth or delay guarantees.
任何带宽或延迟保证。
In internet, you cannot specify that.
在互联网上，你无法指定这一点。
You cannot say I want 10 megabytes per second.
你不能说我想要每秒10兆字节。
You cannot say,
你不能这样说，
I want these packets need to believe delivery 100 millisecond.
我希望这些数据包的传递时间保持在100毫秒内。
What I mentioned to you,
我向你提到的是，
I mentioned earlier that, in general,
我之前提到过，总的来说，
the transfer protocol,
传输协议
the transport layer can provide that.
传输层可以提供这个功能。
But I am telling you now is that transport protocols in the internet
现在我告诉你的是互联网中的传输协议。
do not provide this kind of
请不要提供这种类型的信息。
then that be like our boundaries guarantees.
那就像是我们的边界保证。
Also if a session with a connection,
如果一个会话有一个连接，
if you try to migrate an application from one or to another,
如果你尝试将一个应用程序从一个地方迁移到另一个地方，
they using yummy migration or something like that,
他们正在使用美味迁移或类似的工具。
the connection is not preserved.
连接未保持。
We have another question.
我们有另一个问题。
The questions are reports used to differentiate which packet to send
这些问题是用来区分要发送的数据包的报告。
to different processes on the house.
分配给房子上的不同进程。
Yes.
是的。
Exactly.
没错。
For that.
为此。
Different processes will have different ports numbers when they open a production.
当不同的进程打开一个端口时，它们会有不同的端口号。
That is the application layer.
那是应用层。
Is here any service provided to the end users.
这里是否提供给最终用户的服务？
This application is like the interface depends on the application,
这个应用程序的界面取决于应用程序本身。
protocol depends on the application.
协议取决于应用程序。
In the osi architecture,
在OSI架构中，
there are also a was a transport,
还有一个运输方式，
sorry, was a session on the presentation layer.
抱歉，这是关于表示层的一个会话。
They are not existent in the internet protocol.
它们在互联网协议中不存在。
So be happy.
所以要快乐。
We only need to learn about five really four layers instead of seven.
我们只需要学习五个层次，而不是七个。
This father, their function,
这是父函数，它们的功能是什么？
it is absorbed by the application layer data.
它被应用层数据所吸收。
This is a better step.
这是一个更好的步骤。
You see, kind of the waterfall.
你看，有点像瀑布。
A packet at one level,
在一个层次上的数据包
becomes a payload as a set as the next level,
成为下一级的有效载荷集合。
as you go down the stack.
随着你向下遍历堆栈。
And when you are going to go up the stack,
当你要向上移动堆栈时，
you are going to strip headers after header until you get to generate
你将会剥离头部，直到找到generate位置。
the first layers,
第一层，
physical layer data link layer network layer are implemented by the host
物理层、数据链路层和网络层由主机实现。
and by the roots.
并且通过根部。
The switch is not shown here by the switch implement the physical layer
这里没有显示交换机，但交换机实现了物理层。
and italic layer.
斜体层。
The host implement transport and application layer is throughout the broad implement.
主机实现的传输层和应用层是广泛实现的。
And the protocol is between two ps at the same time.
这个协议是同时在两个进程之间进行的。
Some announcements discussion will be recorded because of the thanksgiving.
由于感恩节的原因，部分讨论将会被录制。
The office hours for wednesday, thursday,
周三和周四的办公时间是：
friday are going to be canceled against because of the thanksgiving.
由于感恩节，星期五的活动将被取消。
The middle three reviewer session is coming next monday.
下周一将进行中间的三个评审会议。
The time is to be determined.
时间待定。
Please stay focused.
请保持专注。
You are going to announce it on piazza.
你将在 Piazza 上宣布这个消息。
The medium three is next wednesday between 7:00 and 9:00 pm and homeworks
期中考试将于下周三晚上7点至9点进行，还有作业。
is released.
已发布。
And is it has been released and is due on friday.
它已经发布了，并且截止日期是星期五。
December 3rd are layers,
12月3日是图层。
five and six used explicitly in other systems,
在其他系统中明确使用了五和六。
or are they obsolete everywhere?
还是它们在任何地方都已经过时了？
They were used by other network protocol and network stacks.
它们被其他网络协议和网络堆栈使用。
In the past, there are many of them,
过去，有很多这样的情况。
but all of them are obsolete.
但它们都已经过时了。
Eventually the internet protocol took over and everyone knows provide
最终，互联网协议占据了主导地位，现在每个人都知道提供。
the internet protocol.
互联网协议
So the answer to your question today are obsolete.
所以你今天的问题的答案已经过时了。
Previous recording letter will be applauded,
之前的录音信件将受到赞赏，
recording, recorded letter.
录音，已录制的信件。
It should be.
应该是的。
We'll make sure that it's upload it.
我们会确保它已经上传了。
Sorry about that.
很抱歉。
Now let's switch the gears.
现在让我们换个话题。
And this is a very interesting aspect of the internet.
这是互联网的一个非常有趣的方面。
It's called end to end argument.
这被称为端到端原则。
If you look about this another way to look at the internet protocol stack,
如果你从另一个角度来看互联网协议栈的话，
its shape is what is called our glass.
它的形状被称为我们的玻璃杯。
What this means that the internet protocol is and is a waste of the howard glass.
这句话的意思是互联网协议是一个浪费霍华德·格拉斯的东西。
And that's why internet probable is so important.
这就是为什么互联网可能如此重要的原因。
And the sorry,
对不起，
internet in ip layer is so important in the internet network stuff,
在互联网网络中，IP层中的互联网非常重要。
because it's kind of unique.
因为它有点独特。
So everyone has to implement the internet protocol interface.
所以每个人都需要实现互联网协议接口。
But under the internet protocol,
但在互联网协议下，
player and above it,
玩家并在其上方,
there is a large variety of different protocols at different layers.
在不同的层级上有许多不同的协议。
You can answer it under the internet protocol.
你可以在互联网协议下进行回答。
You can have different data link layers.
你可以有不同的数据链路层。
You can have different physical layers about above.
你可以在上面使用不同的物理层。
You can have different transport protocols,
你可以使用不同的传输协议，
this pngdp about you have different application protocols.
这个PNGDP是关于你有不同的应用协议。
Right?
对吗？
This is beautiful.
这真是太美了。
The reason is beautiful because it decouple the evolution of the layers
这个原因很美，因为它解耦了层的演化。
of the layers under
在下层的层级中
the underneath and of the layer above.
下方和上方的层次。
Remember it when he discussed the level of indirection.
当他讨论间接级别时，请记住这一点。
Last,
最后,
this is it.
就是这样了。
But I do remember the couple the evolution above from the evolution of the last.
但我确实记得上面的进化与上次的进化相比。
Therefore, if i'm going to add a new data link layer,
因此，如果我要添加一个新的数据链路层，
as long as i'm providing on top of it,
只要我在其之上提供。
ip interface,
IP接口
then all the other application,
然后所有其他应用程序，
all of the other layers above ip should work without any check.
IP层以上的所有其他层应该在没有任何检查的情况下正常工作。
The same.
一样的。
If i'm going to invent a new transport protocol or a new application protocol,
如果我要发明一种新的传输协议或应用协议，
I can do that.
我可以做到。
And as long as i'm going to write against the ip interface,
只要我打算写针对IP接口的代码，
none of the layers below the ip should care that.
IP协议以下的所有层都不需要关心这个问题。
Now there is a new application protocol or a new transport protocol.
现在有一个新的应用协议或者一个新的传输协议。
This is why the ip layer is so fundamental.
这就是为什么IP层如此基础的原因。
This is what we discussed.
这是我们讨论的内容。
So a single internet module player allows arbitrary networks to operate,
因此，一个单独的互联网模块播放器可以使任意网络运行。
allows application to functions on all networks.
允许应用程序在所有网络上运行。
And therefore,
因此，
because the players below and the layers above can evolved separately,
因为下方的玩家和上方的层次可以分别发展。
this is how you also involve the innovation.
这是你如何参与创新的方式。
It enables innovation.
它促进创新。
However,
然而，
changing ip itself is very hard,
更改IP地址本身是非常困难的。
because it's only one layer of a proof point.
因为这只是一个证明点的一层。
The transition from ipv four to ibv six was very painful,
从IPv4过渡到IPv6非常痛苦。
probably don't like 20 years.
可能不喜欢20年。
Now,
现在，
the layers,
层级
it's a very nice construction, very logical, very clear.
这是一个非常好的结构，非常合乎逻辑，非常清晰。
I provide a lot of isolation because one layer can only use a service
我提供了很多隔离，因为每个层级只能使用一个服务。
of the layer below it.
它的下一层。
At the same time, he has some drawbacks,
同时，他也有一些缺点，
because the layer may need some same functionality like false tolerance
因为该层可能需要一些与容错性相似的功能。
of no reliability.
不可靠的。
Some players are going to replicate this function of it.
一些玩家打算复制它的功能。
The layering can also hurt the performance because one layer can hide
分层也可能会影响性能，因为一个层级可能会隐藏掉其他层级的信息。
information from the above layer.
来自上一层的信息。
Like I mentioned to you,
就像我之前跟你提到的一样，
it's one classic example is that the data link layer hides,
其中一个经典例子是数据链路层的隐藏功能。
wire packet was lost.
数据包丢失。
The ip layer hides while the packet was lost.
当数据包丢失时，IP层会隐藏这个事实。
The transfer layer which provides for recent bcp which is provide reliability,
传输层提供了最近的可靠性，这是通过提供可靠性机制来实现的。
and it needs to do the transmission of the packets.
它需要进行数据包的传输。
It cannot make the right the best decision,
它无法做出最佳决策。
because it doesn't know where there is a packet, for instance, was lost,
因为它不知道数据包的位置，例如，数据包可能丢失了。
because it was dropping the matter because of congestion.
由于拥塞问题，它放弃了这个事情。
So therefore, I need to slow down when I send a new packet,
因此，当我发送新的数据包时，我需要减慢速度。
but I retransmit the loss packet,
但是我重新传输了丢失的数据包，
or the packet may have been lost,
或者数据包可能已丢失，
because interference case in which I don't need to slow down.
因为干扰情况下我不需要减速。
But without having this information,
但是如果没有这些信息，
I need to make a decision the decision today to slow down,
我今天需要做出一个决定，即放慢速度。
which is not optimal, for instance, for wireless networks.
这并不是最优的选择，比如对于无线网络来说。
Some of the layers are not always clearly separate.
有些层次并不总是清晰地分离开来。
The other thing is that you had, as you remember,
另外一件事是，你记得的话，
like for each layer at its own head,
每个层级都有自己的头指针。
you have a lot of head ups and that overhead,
你有很多负担和额外开销，
because it's not really data you want to send in some cases ahead.
因为在某些情况下，你并不真正想要提前发送数据。
That is much harder than the actual data you want to send.
这比你实际想要发送的数据要困难得多。
So now,
所以现在，
again,
再次，
you have all these layers and you want to implement some functionality.
你有所有这些层级，并且想要实现一些功能。
The one question is,
问题是，
at once layer, you are implementing that function.
在当前层次，你正在实现那个函数。
And the end to end arguments is a principle which tries to answer that question.
端到端论证是一种原则，试图回答这个问题。
Some people say is a sacred text of the internet.
有些人说这是互联网的圣经。
And like any sacred text,
就像任何神圣的文本一样，
there are endless disputes about what exactly means.
关于"what exactly means"的确切含义存在无休止的争议。
Right?
对吗？
And everyone cites the supporting their position that it's a little bit a
每个人都引用支持他们立场的论据，认为这是有点的。
like the bible,
像圣经一样，
but still, it's very important.
但是，这仍然非常重要。
But let's consider this, for instance,
但是让我们考虑一下这个例子，
some function into like reliability or security.
一些功能涉及可靠性或安全性。
It's obviously, where do you implement the italian man,
显然，你要在哪里实现这个意大利人呢？
ib land and the metal layer,
IB Land和金属层
transport layer where and why?
传输层位于计算机网络的协议栈中，位于网络层之上和应用层之下。传输层的主要目的是提供端到端的数据传输服务，确保数据在网络中的可靠传输和正确接收。
传输层的主要功能包括：
1. 分段和重组：将应用层的数据分割成较小的数据段，并在接收端重新组装成完整的数据。
2. 连接管理：建立、维护和终止端到端的连接，包括连接的建立、数据传输和连接的关闭。
3. 流量控制：通过控制发送端的发送速率，确保接收端能够及时处理和接收数据，避免数据丢失或拥塞。
4. 差错控制：通过校验和、确认和重传机制，保证数据的可靠传输，检测和纠正传输过程中的错误。
传输层的设计目标是提供一种通用的、可靠的数据传输服务，使得应用程序能够方便地进行数据交换和通信。通过传输层的协议，应用程序可以不必关心底层网络的细节，而只需要关注数据的发送和接收。
And our application can implement that.
我们的应用程序可以实现这个。
And the main point here is that like,
这里的主要观点是，就像...
we'll see in the next example,
我们将在下一个例子中看到，
is that because a network,
这是因为网络的原因吗？
even if they want at a lower level of the network,
即使他们希望在网络的较低层级进行操作，
cannot implement,
无法实现
and to end and end,
结束和结束。
function will be corrected.
该函数将被修正。
The application may anyway have to implement.
该应用程序可能仍然需要实现。
Let's take a following example,
让我们来看一个例子，
but I it's okay.
没问题。
It's an example.
这是一个例子。
Say you want to transfer a lively a file from one host on us
假设你想要在美国的两台主机之间传输一个活跃的文件。
how this will look like.
这会是什么样子。
If you want to build an application,
如果你想要构建一个应用程序，
where is the data from the file?
文件中的数据在哪里？
Then you send it over the network from hostile to hostile.
然后你将它从一个敌对主机发送到另一个敌对主机。
The horse bees and the application from horse b is going to write it
马蜂和马b的应用程序将要编写它。
on the disk,
在磁盘上
be this is how you copy a file.
这是如何复制文件的方法。
Now, if I want to have a reliable transfer, what you are going to do,
现在，如果我想要进行可靠的传输，你将要做什么？
there are the solutions.
这是解决方案。
I make each of these thread steps reliable.
我使每个线程步骤都可靠。
And now I can catalyze them.
现在我可以催化它们了。
I have here are five reliable steps,
我这里有五个可靠的步骤，
entrance that must be reliable.
必须可靠的入口。
The second one,
第二个。
I don't know any of those that seems.
我不知道任何一个看起来是这样的。
But after I get all,
但是在我得到一切之后，
what I am told is a file,
我被告知的是一个文件。
i'm going to computer checks out,
我要去电脑检查。
and i'm going to send to to match against the jackson,
我将发送它与杰克逊进行匹配。
sent by the host by the sender.
由发送方发送的由主机发送的消息。
So basically hosting,
基本上，托管服务是指将一个或多个网站、应用程序或其他在线服务存储在由第三方提供的服务器上。这些服务器通常位于数据中心，具备高速互联网连接和稳定的电力供应，以确保服务的可靠性和可用性。通过托管服务，用户可以将自己的网站或应用程序部署到互联网上，而无需自己购买和维护服务器硬件和网络设备。托管服务提供商通常还提供额外的功能和支持，如数据备份、安全性和性能优化等。
when he sends a file, it computes also a check stop.
当他发送一个文件时，它还会计算一个校验码。
He sends out the file to horse, be,
他将文件发送给horse和be。
the horse be takes against a file, save the file.
将马对着文件，保存文件。
And also, after it saves the file,
而且，在保存文件之后，
its entire file,
整个文件
it computes a check sum and our computer check sum of the, say,
它计算一个校验和，我们的计算机也计算一个校验和，比如说，
file with the check sum sent by the whole state.
包含整个状态的校验和的文件。
If they are the same success,
如果它们取得相同的成功，
If they are not the same, send the file again,
如果它们不相同，请重新发送文件。
which of the solutions are going to be?
哪个解决方案将会被采用？
If it were for you and one
如果是为了你和另一个人
edison say solution one because solution three is bad for large files,
Edison说方案一是因为方案三对于大文件来说不太好。
through solution three is bad for large files.
通过解决方案三对于大文件来说是不好的。
Assignment.
作业。
I like solution to anyone else.
我喜欢解决方案适用于其他人。
Simon, why do you like some shampoo?
Simon，你为什么喜欢某种洗发水？
Because I don't know whether between each steps is my break.
因为我不知道每个步骤之间是否有我的休息时间。
That's correct.
没错。
Great answer.
很棒的答案。
So that you see the point is that here,
所以你明白这里的要点是什么了，
if I concatenate five reliable steps,
如果我将五个可靠的步骤连接起来，
it doesn't mean that end to end.
这并不意味着端到端。
Everything is reliable.
一切都是可靠的。
Right?
对吗？
This is the grain is a solution, though.
这个解决方案是可行的。
It's checking the checks out.
这是在检查支票。
The solution is incomplete,
解决方案不完整，
because what happens?
因为发生了什么事情？
For instance, when I copy the data from the disk to the application memory,
例如，当我将数据从磁盘复制到应用程序内存时，
and the application memory is corrupted,
应用程序的内存已损坏，
but luck fundamentally,
但是运气基本上是幸运的，
because I cannot guarantee that the end the solution one,
因为我无法保证最终的解决方案是唯一的。
it's is correct.
是的，这是正确的。
I need any way to do a check sum and verify
我需要任何一种方法来进行校验和验证。
the main point here that the application,
这里的主要观点是应用程序，
anyway, has to implement the functionality to verify the checks out,
无论如何，必须实现验证支票的功能。
even if you solution one.
即使你解决了一个问题。
So therefore,
因此，
the full functionality of reliability can be implemented as the application
可靠性的全部功能可以作为应用程序来实现。
level.
级别。
The network doesn't going to do anything.
网络不会做任何事情。
Now,
现在，
for correctness reasons,
出于正确性的考虑，
right?
是的，正确的。
It's a game.
这是一个游戏。
It's enough to implement the application.
实现应用程序就足够了。
The network doesn't do anything.
网络没有做任何事情。
Still,
然而，
we are just talking that the network also implement reliability and not
我们只是在讨论网络也需要实现可靠性，而不是
the natural transformation,
自然变换
reliability.
可靠性。
So why would sales and effort implement reliably?
那么为什么销售和努力要可靠地实施呢？
They are reliable for a reliable product?
他们可靠吗？他们的产品可靠吗？
It's not necessary for correctness.
这并不是必需的，不影响正确性。
We just conclude that,
我们刚刚得出结论，
but still,
但是，
you may want another to implement elaborate.
你可能需要另一个人来实施详细的操作。
Why is that to avoid very expensive collection?
为什么要避免非常昂贵的收集过程？
Alexander?
是的，我是Alexander。有什么我可以帮助您的吗？
So if you think about,
所以如果你考虑一下，
right?
对的？
It's in the second solution,
这是在第二个解决方案中。
if you have ten gigabytes size five,
如果你有十个千兆字节大小的文件，
if one bite 1 bit,
如果一个字节是1比特的话，
not on bite, 1 bit is corrupted.
不会咬人，只有1个比特位损坏了。
You need to resend the entire ten gigabytes.
你需要重新发送整个十千兆字节的文件。
However,
然而，
if you have,
如果你有的话，
the network is reliable.
网络是可靠的。
And the
而且
that's perfect.
太好了。
So the question is that should I implement this function
所以问题是我应该实现这个函数吗？
at the lower levels or not?
在较低的层次上吗？
The question is the answer here.
问题就是答案。
It depends,
这取决于情况。
right?
是的，正确的。
Because in and and the reason this is a
因为在和和这个原因是这样的
question is that if you implement the function,
问题是，如果你实现了这个函数，
it is a lower layer.
它是一个较低的层次。
This function, I it doesn't reduce the application complexity,
这个函数并没有减少应用程序的复杂性。
because you anyway,
因为无论如何，
into implement there and increase another complexity.
将其实现在那里并增加另一个复杂度。
Worse yet,
更糟糕的是，
it can increase,
它可以增加，
it can add overhead to application which do not read that functional.
对于不使用该功能的应用程序来说，它可能会增加额外的开销。
Like, for instance, if you have a voice over ip telephony over the internet,
例如，如果你在互联网上使用语音传输IP电话技术，
in that particular case,
在那种特殊情况下，
reliability is not helpful,
可靠性没有帮助，
because you need to satisfy,
因为你需要满足，
you need to the latency is more important than getting every every packet.
你需要明白延迟比获取每个数据包更重要。
Correct?
正确吗？
Like if the sound is a little bit distorted,
如果声音有点失真，
it's probably it's okay.
可能没问题。
But if we need to wait for a second to return in the packet,
但是如果我们需要等待一秒钟才能返回数据包，
that's probably not.
那可能不是。
Okay.
好的。
Yeah,
是的，
it was glitch.
这是一个故障。
So I don't know what will happen also is recording because on my side,
所以我不知道会发生什么，也不确定是否正在录制，因为在我的这一端，
it said a little bit recording is in progress.
正在进行少量录音。
I hope that it's just a glitch.
我希望这只是一个小故障。
So that didn't mean anything for the recording.
这对于录音来说没有任何意义。
That is a the great timing while we are discussing about entrant reliability.
这正是我们讨论参赛者可靠性的好时机。
Anyway,
无论如何，
so basically,
所以基本上，
you can implement a net of function is at a lower level stack.
你可以在较低级别的堆栈中实现一个函数的网络。
If we can improve performance.
如果我们能提高性能。
Now there are different interpretation of the end to end argument.
现在对于端到端原则有不同的解释。
And one extreme implementation, he says,
他说，还有一种极端的实现方式，
even if you can improve efficiency,
即使你能提高效率，
don't bother if you cannot simplify the application or the cost software,
如果你无法简化应用程序或成本软件，就不要费心了。
don't buy to implement as another player.
不要购买以实施为另一个玩家。
This is very conservative.
这非常保守。
I have the moderating term in interpretation.
我对解释中的调节术语有了解。
So the moderate interpretation is kind of it's it basically says you
所以温和的解释基本上是说，它表示你
can implement the function.
可以实现这个函数。
It is a network, but be careful about that.
这是一个网络，但要小心。
Think twice.
三思而后行。
In particular,
特别是，
you can implement the function id at a lower layer,
你可以在更低的层次上实现函数id。
if and only if doesn't impose a burden on applications that do not require
如果且仅当不会对不需要的应用程序造成负担
that functionality.
那个功能。
And it provides a significant, improving platform.
它提供了一个重要且不断改进的平台。
So the benefits are out waiting the complexity of the implementation.
因此，好处超过了实施的复杂性。
And by the way,
顺便说一下，
you shouldn't be a burden for the applications who do not need that function.
你不应该成为那些不需要该功能的应用程序的负担。
So if the application doesn't need for reliability,
如果应用程序不需要可靠性，
you shouldn't suffer.
你不应该受苦。
For instance, should that experience?
例如，应该有那种经验吗？
Have you like latency and relatives and you say interpretation we are using?
你是否喜欢延迟和相关性，并且你所说的解释是我们正在使用的解释吗？
Okay?
好的？
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
So again, you have a functionality like reliability,
所以，你需要的是类似可靠性的功能，
which you must for being to be absolute,
为了成为绝对的，你必须这样做。
to be correct to ensure correctness.
确保正确性是正确的。
You have to implement the application level at the end.
你需要在最后实现应用层。
Hosts the question.
托管问题。
Should we also implement the liability of the lower layers?
我们是否还应该实现较低层的责任？
Is another layers.
还有其他层次。
The answer here,
这里的答案是
according to the moderate interpretation of the entrant argument,
根据参与者论点的适度解释，
but the bad for that is pretty high.
但是这样做的风险相当高。
You can implement the liability another team.
你可以实施责任给另一个团队。
Only if you get significant increase improvement in the performance,
只有在性能显著提升的情况下，才会生效。
you are not going to hurt the application.
你不会对应用程序造成任何伤害。
We do not need that function.
我们不需要那个功能。
Any questions?
有任何问题吗？
Now we are going to start one of the last topics of the course.
现在我们将开始课程的最后一个主题之一。
This is flow control.
这是流量控制。
So the flow control,
因此，流量控制，
remember,
记住，
assures that a fast sender does not overwhelm a slow receiver.
确保快速发送方不会压垮慢速接收方。
And we already seen some mechanics,
我们已经看到了一些机制，
like producer, consumers is bounded buffers.
像生产者一样，消费者也是有界缓冲区。
So remember, in this case,
所以记住，在这种情况下，
you cannot overpower the consumer,
你不能压制消费者。
overwhelmed the consumer.
使消费者不知所措。
Because if the buffer is full,
因为如果缓冲区已满，
the producer can no longer put packets in the buffer.
生产者无法再将数据包放入缓冲区。
The buffer is naturally pushing back on the producer.
缓冲区自然地对生产者进行了阻力反作用。
One is full, accepts no new items.
一个已满，不接受新项目。
Therefore, if the consumer is slower,
因此，如果消费者速度较慢，
the producer is going to adapt to the consumer speed
生产者将会适应消费者的速度。
because of the bounded buffer.
因为有界缓冲区。
So that's the idea.
那就是这个想法。
In the case of the tcp and this is a talk about this, be flow control.
在TCP的情况下，我们要讨论的是流量控制。
Things are more complicated because they are not on the same machine.
事情变得更加复杂，因为它们不在同一台机器上。
We are on different machines.
我们在不同的机器上。
And with an unreliable network can be doing dcp choosing what is
在网络不稳定的情况下，进行动态连接性协议（DCP）选择可能会出现问题。
called a sliding window protocol as a byte and not packet level.
被称为滑动窗口协议，以字节而不是数据包为单位。
And there are 22 types go back and is this a bit a hole
有22种类型的回退，这是有点麻烦的。
near and selectively be disappeared?
附近和有选择性地消失？
The star hall,
星星大厅
new reno and sack,
新雷诺和萨克
are the different types of pc ps.
计算机有不同类型的电源吗？
We are going to talk about more about them,
我们将会更多地讨论它们。
a little next lecture,
下一节课会稍微讲一下。
go back and meeting.
回去开会。
Here is a difference.
这是一个区别。
We explain the packet level.
我们解释一下数据包级别。
Before it's easier.
以前更容易。
I sent them packets.
我发送了数据包给他们。
And the 5/5 packet was lost.
第5个数据包丢失了。
The receiver gets the first four packets,
接收方收到了前四个数据包。
and then the last five packets,
然后是最后五个数据包，
1234, and 6789, 10.
1234和6789，10。
Please go back.
请返回。
And you are going to go back and resent from back at 5:00.
你将返回并重新发送自5:00开始的消息。
So i'm going to pretend five,
所以我要假装是五岁的样子
and 6789, 10,
和 6789、10,
despite the fact the 6798, 10,
尽管事实是6798, 10,
we have already received by the receipt by the spiders, by the recipient.
我们已经通过蜘蛛收到了收据，通过收件人。
So you miss something,
所以你错过了一些东西，
you restart from that missing packet,
你从丢失的数据包重新开始。
all the way selective repeat like the name implies.
全程选择重传（Selective Repeat）正如其名称所示。
If you lose a packet in our previous examples, a packet five,
如果在我们之前的示例中丢失了一个数据包，例如第五个数据包，
we send only back at five.
我们只在五点之后回复。
Why doesn't everyone implement selective repeat,
为什么不是每个人都实现选择重传？
which seems much easier,
这似乎更容易，
much in a much more efficient?
更加高效的多？
Because it's more complex.
因为它更复杂。
Go back and is my simple thing for all the less efficient.
回溯并简化所有不高效的事情。
Now is the dcp flow control.
现在是数据通信协议的流量控制。
The receiver tells us that how many more buys it can receive
接收器告诉我们它还可以接收多少个购买请求。
without overflowing this buffer.
在不溢出缓冲区的情况下。
I'm going to tell you I can receive 1 kilowatt.
我要告诉你我可以接收1千瓦。
And in some way,
在某种程度上，
this tells you that you can send me one kilobyte of data before you hear
这告诉你，在你听到之前，你可以发送给我一千字节的数据。
from me whether I receive anything.
我是否收到任何东西。
Right?
对吗？
Because you're now based on what I told you that I can get one kilobyte,
因为根据我告诉你的信息，我可以得到一千字节。
but because you cannot send me more to be before you hear from me that
但是因为在听到我的回复之前你不能给我发送更多信息
like you can send more.
你可以发送更多。
This is advertising.
这是广告。
Now, like I mentioned,
现在，就像我之前提到的，
for the pcp the protocol is not at the packet level as a byte level.
对于PCP（Packet Copy Protocol），协议的操作不是在数据包级别，而是在字节级别。
The acknowledgment as a recipient, i'm telling you,
作为收件人的确认，我告诉你，
i'm acknowledgment, contain the sequence number of a byte of the next byte.
我明白了，确认消息中包含下一个字节的序列号。
The receiver expects.
接收方期望。
This means that i'm telling you that acknowledgment contains a number,
这意味着我告诉你确认包含一个数字。
the sequence number 100.
序列号为100。
This means that I received,
这意味着我收到了。
i'm telling you implicitly that I received all the bytes up to 99.
我在暗示你，我已经接收到了从第一个字节到第99个字节的所有数据。
There is no gap.
没有间隙。
All of them up to a 99.
所有的都达到了99分。
And the sequence number is start to count.
而且序列号开始计数。
It's like, is from the fast first byte.
就好像，是从第一个字节开始的。
So the first byte, which will send up to the connection of that.
所以第一个字节将发送到该连接。
Right?
对吗？
This is a very simple diagram showing the sending process,
这是一个非常简单的图示，展示了发送过程。
the receiving process.
接收进程。
And the buffer are the receiver.
缓冲区是接收者。
The dcpip is implemented in the kernel.
dcpip 在内核中实现。
Remember,
记住，
what you discussed is about bsd unix bsd we said that
你们讨论的是关于BSD Unix的内容，我们说过了。
the dcpip is part of that was first implemented
DCPIP是首次实施的一部分。
in the bsdi think,
在BSDI的观点中，
4.3 version.
4.3 版本。
And it's part of your legacy is one of the biggest achievements
这是你的遗产之一，也是最大的成就之一。
in the open source software,
在开源软件中，
because that's internet.
因为那就是互联网。
Why do you do that?
为什么你这样做？
Also?
还有什么其他问题吗？
That is because you cannot do context switching.
这是因为你无法进行上下文切换。
You cannot do it application level again,
你不能再在应用层面上做这个操作了。
performance at one garbage per second.
每秒处理一个垃圾的性能。
Typically, the packers have been 1,500 bytes,
通常情况下，打包程序的大小为1,500字节。
the ip packets.
IP数据包。
This takes to send, like one garbage per second is 12 set of micro seconds.
发送一个垃圾信息需要大约一秒钟的时间，即每秒钟发送12个微秒的垃圾信息。
And if it's 100 bytes packets,
如果是100字节的数据包，
it's lesson on my one microsecond.
这是我一微秒的课程。
And by the way, one gap is per second is slow.
顺便说一下，每秒一个间隔太慢了。
Today we are talking about ten cabbies per second,
今天我们要讨论每秒十辆出租车的问题。
40 cabbies per second,
每秒40辆出租车。
100 cabbies per second connection.
每秒连接100辆出租车。
There is no way you can do context.
你无法进行上下文处理。
Switching starts that fast to send every packet,
切换速度如此之快，以至于能够立即发送每个数据包。
the application to send every packet.
应用程序发送每个数据包。
And actually,
实际上，
there is not only one buffer.
不只有一个缓冲区。
There are multiple buffers.
有多个缓冲区。
There is a buffer, which is between the process and in process.
有一个缓冲区，位于进程和正在进行的过程之间。
The piano.
钢琴。
Again, you cannot have contact switching on every packet.
再次强调，你不能在每个数据包上都进行上下文切换。
Then it's between the receiving operating system that the operating system
在这种情况下，操作系统之间的通信是在接收操作系统之间进行的。
on the receiving force and the receiving process.
关于接收力和接收过程。
And then you have a buffer actually,
然后你实际上有一个缓冲区，
between the two hosts as atcpiip level, the transport level.
在两个主机之间，TCP/IP协议栈的传输层起到了重要的作用。
There is a buffer that operating system on the recipient cost is maintaining,
接收方操作系统维护着一个缓冲区。
you get the packets from the sending post.
你从发送端获取数据包。
So here it's in more details how things that happen.
这里更详细地描述了事情发生的过程。
You have this buffer here,
你这里有一个缓冲区。
and you have this buffer here.
你在这里有一个缓冲区。
You see me at the end,
你在最后看到我，
host and whispering host.
主机和悄悄主机。
And but I tell you,
但是我告诉你，
so you have the state buyers to produce our consumers sending process,
所以您有国家采购商来生产我们的消费者发送过程，
sending pcb sending dcp receiving pcb receiving dcp receiving process.
发送进程控制块（PCB），发送数据控制块（DCP），接收进程控制块（PCB），接收数据控制块（DCP），接收进程。
Let's take up of these examples.
让我们来看看这些例子。
They say the maximal ip packet size is 100 bytes.
他们说最大的IP数据包大小是100字节。
The size of the receiving buffer is the receiving buffer,
接收缓冲区的大小是指接收缓冲区的容量。
is 300 by bytes.
是以字节为单位的300。
Recall, the acknowledgment indicates the next expected byte in sequence,
回顾一下，确认信息表示下一个预期的字节序号。
not the last recite received byte.
不是最后接收的字节。
We assume that these are circular buffers.
我们假设这些是循环缓冲区。
What is a circular buffer?
什么是循环缓冲区？
A buffer has a size of n you may have an infinite sequence of bytes
一个缓冲区的大小为n，你可能有一个无限字节序列。
and a bite.
还有一口。
We sequence number k is stored in a location with the index k mod and+1 in
我们将序列号k存储在索引为k mod (n+1)的位置上。
the buffer.
缓冲区。
This is a for example,
这是一个例子，
these are sequence numbers of hello world.
这些是"Hello World"的序列号。
So say, age is a sequence number 27.
所以说，年龄是一个序列号为27的数字。
And l the last l is sequence number 76.
最后一个L的序列号是76。
And the buffer has only ten entries.
缓冲区只有十个条目。
Right?
对吗？
Then this is how you map it.
那么这是你如何进行映射的方式。
27 is 27 mod n it's seven,
27是27除以n的余数，它是七。
because any stand and+1, it's eight.
因为任何数加1，结果都是八。
So n plus,
所以n加上，
was it so sorry?
很抱歉吗？
This is age.
这是年龄。
We are looking at e which is sequence number 28,
我们正在查看序列号为28的e。
sequence number twenty eight twenty eight, more ten,
序列号二八二八，再加十，
+1 is mine.
+1 是我的。
This is how this data is a buffer data from e to r the blue,
这是从e到r的蓝色数据的缓冲数据。
which is in blue, shown in blue,
是蓝色的，以蓝色显示的
is a buffer in the simpler buffer.
一个简单的缓冲区中有一个缓冲区。
Initially,
最初，
we are going to have a bunch of variables which. two different
我们将会有一堆变量，其中两个是不同的。
things in the buffer,
缓冲区中的内容
three on the sending part,
发送端的三个部分，
three on the receiving part.
接收方有三个。
You have last bite to be done,
你还剩最后一口要吃完了，
which is the last byte written by sending process.
发送进程写入的最后一个字节是哪个？
Last by scent is a last byte,
"Last by scent is a last byte" 可以翻译为 "最后一位是最后一个字节"。
send by sender to the receiver.
发送者发送给接收者。
Last byte act is a last act byte by the receiver is a sender.
"Last byte act" 是接收方的最后一个字节行为，由发送方完成。
Last byte received now is on the receiving side.
现在接收端已经收到了最后一个字节。
Is the last bite received by the receiver from sender.
接收方是否收到了发送方的最后一个字节。
Next bite expected is the last in sequence byte expected by receiver.
接收方期望的下一个字节是序列中的最后一个字节。
And the last byte read is the last bite read by the receiving process.
最后一个字节读取是接收进程读取的最后一个字节。
Actually, for the next byte expected,
实际上，对于下一个预期的字节，
this should be the next in sequence by the expected by the cigarette,
这应该是根据香烟的预期顺序的下一个。
not last.
不是最后的。
Okay.
好的。
Now the advertised window is a number of bytes like we decide the disappear
现在，广告窗口的大小是以字节为单位的，就像我们决定的那样消失。
receiver can receive.
接收方可以接收。
So what is this one?
这是什么？
Let's say with blue here,
假设我们用蓝色来表示这里，
a is a bite which are already in the receiving the receiver buffer.
a 是一个已经在接收缓冲区中的字节。
The advertising window is a maximum receive buffer.
广告窗口是一个最大接收缓冲区。
It's a maximum buffer size minus the last bite
这是最大缓冲区大小减去最后一个字节。
received this one,
收到了这个。
and the difference between the last byte received and last by thread.
最后一个字节接收到的值与最后一个线程接收到的值之间的差异。
Right?
对吗？
So basically, this is,
基本上，这是...
You need to subtract from the maximum received buffer.
你需要从最大接收缓冲区中减去。
So from the buffer size of the receiver,
从接收器的缓冲区大小来看，
how many bytes are still in the buffer,
缓冲区中还剩多少字节？
which are not yet read by the receiving process?
还没有被接收进程读取的是哪些？
On the sending process side is similar to you have a sender window,
在发送进程的一侧，类似于你有一个发送窗口，
which is a number of buys atcp sender can send.
这是ATCP发送方可以发送的购买数量。
And the center window is advertised window minus last by cent,
中心窗口是广告窗口减去最后一个百分比。
minus last by act.
减去最后一个操作。
Intuitively,
直观地说，
this means that I can send as a sender.
这意味着我可以作为发送者发送信息。
I can send a number of bytes,
我可以发送一定数量的字节。
which is by subtracting what you told me that you can receive,
这是通过减去你告诉我的你可以接收的内容来实现的。
what I always send,
我总是发送的内容
I haven't heard from it.
我还没有收到任何消息。
And I'm finishing with this example.
我完成了这个例子。
Say you told me the advertising window is one kilobyte.
你告诉我广告窗口的大小是一千字节。
And since you told me that the advertising window is one kilobyte,
既然你告诉我广告窗口大小是一千字节，
I send you 100 bytes.
我给你发送了100字节的数据。
How many more bytes I can send you without hearing from the answer?
在收到答案之前，您还可以发送多少字节的信息？
It's 900.
是900。
Right?
对吗？
So that's basically what the center window tries to capture.
这基本上就是中心窗口试图捕捉的内容。
Is this.
这是吗？
I'm going to stop here.
我要停在这里了。
And this materials we've done in this lecture,
这节课我们完成了以下的教材内容：
you'll be part of the midterm.
你将参加期中考试。
And again, best of luck with everything and happy sensitive area.
祝你一切顺利，愉快的敏感区域。